[custodian] This guy die or something?
'Cause I get queasy.
If he did. you got to tell me now
'cause I can't be
walking in with no dead body.
I do locks and light bulbs.
Blood isn't my thing.
Can you open it or not?
[custodian] Yeah. I'm trying...
- [Juliette] Mm-hmm.
- ...but these keys aren't working.
Was this Trumbull guy Judicial?
- [Juliette] I'm not at liberty to...
- If so. I'll need a different set.
Maybe tomorrow we can come back...
- With the Forgiveness Holiday...
- Is there another way in?
- [custodian] Yeah. but Judge Meadows...
- [Paul] Sheriff. Hey...
- What are you... Wait. what are you...
- [Juliette grunts]
[switch clicks]
[custodian]
IT distro probably cut the power early.
Yeah. but protocol requires
the power be on...
Can you head to distro
and get the lights back on?
- [custodian] Yeah.
- [Juliette] Great.
You two take the kitchen.
I'm gonna check the bedroom.
- [Molly] What are we looking for?
- [Juliette] For anything strange
that might tell us
why Trumbull killed Marnes.
[cabinet opens]
[objects clattering]
- You go in there yet?
- No. Anything in the front?
Not yet.
[Paul] What the heck is this?
- What you got?
- Honestly. I don't know.
But. uh... [breathes heavily]
We're gonna need a relics bag.
What are you smiling at?
At you. I guess.
[Juliette] You know they call you
Creepy George. right?
They've scratched it on the side
of the generator.
- It says. "Beware of Creepy George."
- Okay. First off...
- "He is so creepy."
- ...you shut up. [chuckles]
- You would never allow generator graffiti.
- Yeah. that's true.
And second.
if you'd said. "creepy computer guy."
I might have believed you.
In fact. Creepy George.
if he really is a thing.
probably just another guy.
Am I your only friend? Like.
I know I'm your only friend down here.
but am I your only friend
in the entire Silo?
'Cause that's pretty sad.
No. no. It's pretty great.
I mean. if I... I... I gotta have one.
You wanna keep that?
What. if I wanna risk going to prison
or sent down to the mines
for one of your strange toys? No.
We already broke into Supply together
so you could have your precious tape.
No. so Mechanical and the Silo
could have its necessary tape.
- And you. sir. did nothing.
- Hey. hey. hey. hey.
[Juliette] No. no. You drew a map.
A really shitty map.
I did everything else by myself.
including throwing bacon at dogs
and running like crazy.
But for a roll of tape.
George. that tape saves lives. okay?
Maybe not IT's shitty tape.
but Mechanical's does.
and that's why I did it.
I didn't take a risk for myself.
I did it for everyone.
and these strange things you have here.
they're just not worth risking a life for.
Especially when you don't know
what they are.
If these things aren't worth
risking our lives for.
why do they make it a risk to our lives
to have them?
[inhales deeply] I don't know.
Neither do I.
These things were used by someone
for something at some point as tools.
I'm gonna use 'em as clues.
It's a stupidly dangerous hobby.
And not all of these things are illegal.
by the way.
[with mouth full] Okay.
This...
may not appear as valuable as...
[scoffs] ...a refurbished socket wrench
or as romantic as flowers from the Mids.
But to me. this watch...
is everything.
[breathes deeply]
And I want to give it to you.
[rattling]
George. it... it's broken.
No. I'm serious. It's like a paperweight
cheaper than the paper it would hold up.
It's a gift.
- [inhales deeply. groans]
- [chuckles]
And in a world filled with a million
unknowns. it is possible that this watch...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and... and crazy relics like these...
- George.
- ...are the key to answering
- the Silo's biggest questions.
- George.
Are you not gonna ask
what the Silo's biggest question is?
Just stop talking. please.
Before you fuck it all up.
[ticking]
[lock clicks]
[computer chimes]
[sighing]
[computer processing]
[computer chimes]
Shit.
You didn't take that to Judicial?
You're in early.
First day you beat me in.
Is that a note for me?
A porter brought it from Recycling.
Keeping an illegal relic
beyond the 12-hour window
from discovery to Judicial handoff
is a serious crime.
Even for a sheriff.
- How do you know it's illegal?
- [Paul] I know that I don't know.
Clause 75A-11: An investigation
into relics may be conducted
by either the sheriff
or the Judicial Department when the re...
When the identified relic
is associated with a serious crime.
I'd say murder qualifies.
You read the next paragraph?
That's only with Judicial's approval.
Which means?
If you want a relics investigation.
you have to see Judge Meadows.
I'm hearing that a lot. Why don't they rip
the pages out of the Pact
and leave one that says.
"See Judge Meadows"?
- [scoffs]
- You've talked to her. right?
She'd pass through the office
when I was at Judicial.
But these days.
even when you win the Pact competition.
it's Sims who gives you the pin.
There's a competition
for knowing the Pact?
- I won it four times.
- Hmm.
- More than anyone else.
- Of course you did.
But I was just a Judicial regular.
You're the sheriff.
If you wanna meet with Meadows.
that's another thing entirely.
[citizens chattering]
[representative] Happy Forgiveness Day.
Today is for unity. family and friends.
- [passerby] Happy Forgiveness Day.
- [Sims] Good morning.
- [Sims] Billings. Sheriff.
- Sims.
- [Sims] How are things?
- [Paul] Good.
- How's Judicial?
- [Sims] Everything is good.
[door lock opens]
[secretary] Judge.
I'm not feeling well.
so let's make this quick.
I'm here about the investigation
into Trumbull.
- I thought that was settled.
- It is.
Well. this was found about ten hours ago
by Deputy Billings
on a search we did with Deputy Karins.
Where?
Trumbull's apartment.
In the bathroom. sir.
[Juliette] I'd like to conduct
a relics investigation
as a way to identify possible
offenders. like Trumbull.
before they have a chance to act.
Judge. the Pact says that the gateway
to disruptive criminal activity
- often starts with unli...
- Unlicensed documents and relics. I know.
But this relic. what is it?
I don't know.
That... That's why I want to look into it.
This didn't belong to Trumbull.
I don't care where you found it.
It isn't his.
You are aware we have files on every relic
found within the last 140 years.
Yeah.
but I looked into the database. and...
I wasn't saying "we" meaning all of us.
I mean "we" as in Judicial.
We have a far more extensive catalog
of information.
For example.
that watch you wear on your wrist.
In Judicial. we know. I know.
that particular item.
despite being in your possession.
is currently registered
to a now-deceased George Wilkins.
A man who you claim was murdered.
Accidents happen.
And Sheriff Becker made me realize
that Wilkins' death was one of them.
That's why I'd like to open
this investigation.
So that we can know those things
that are not in your catalog.
Like the fact that your very close
colleague. Douglas Trumbull.
- was a murderer.
- Sheriff Nichols.
Judge. if I may?
You may.
Let's wrap it up. I wanna get home
before I have to fight through a crowd.
A relics investigation
is actually a smart play.
Especially today
with the Forgiveness Holiday.
people will be more inclined
to turn over items
without facing legal jeopardy.
So. I'm fine with it...
- Okay.
- ...as long as you take Paul with you.
You probably know less of the Pact
- than my son does.
- [scoffs]
You'll need a specialist with you
at all times. creating a list.
Every offense. every relic
and the names of who has what.
Yeah. of course.
[citizens chattering in distance]
- What's the plan?
- You can head back up. See you in an hour.
Sheriff. with Sims taking interest.
Judicial will be watching you
everywhere you go. Every level.
Either his guys or the whispering friends
of the Silo. And they could be anybody.
So. like it or not.
today I'm with you all the way.
[inhales deeply] I know a guy who's been
busted for relics. and he owes me one.
Let's go.
[citizens chattering]
- Ah. fuck me. Who'd I kill this time?
- [Juliette] I've got a relic question.
For someone at this address?
You coming out. or are we going in?
Look. I don't know what Marnes
told you about me. but I'm a simple man.
I paint walls. That's how I make
my living. I don't deal illegal relics.
So. who do I see about legal ones?
Couldn't say.
I don't deal anymore.
Especially things like that.
A watch?
- A working watch. Who the fuck are you?
- [Juliette] Hey. hey.
The old guys at least had the decency
to identify themselves.
I'm Deputy Billings.
The new Deputy Sheriff.
Like I give a fuck.
Sheriff. I don't know what you're looking
for me to do. okay?
But I feel like no matter what I say
or I don't say. you're gonna arrest me.
No. not on the Forgiveness Holiday.
Bullshit. You don't arrest me now.
you put my name on a list put together
by Judicial-face here. And then what?
One day... [stammers]...out of the blue.
I'm just doing law-abiding shit...
- Oh. 'cause you're just a simple man.
- Exactly.
Then there's a knock on the door.
You know what? Not even.
Maybe there's just a sheriff
with a crowbar.
and I'm yanked out of my place
for something I didn't do.
- So. no. I don't. I don't know anyone.
- You know what. Kennedy?
This sheriff is the only reason
you're not in jail.
And you are obviously having regrets.
This is not about you.
We're looking into relics.
That watch is a very peculiar relic
to be using to investigate all relics.
- And it's on your arm...
- [clears throat]
...not in an evidence bag.
which makes me believe
that it's personal to you.
And in my experience.
people with badges doing things
for personal reasons
tend to get other people hurt.
So you're giving us a name.
or are we leaving with yours?
[chuckles]
Your choice.
[Patrick inhales deeply] How about this?
How about you give me the watch.
I try to sell it. and if I do.
I'll give you the name
of the person I sold it to.
How about this?
Shit. Sheriff.
Hey. All... All right.
I need you and Holston Junior
to stop showing up here. okay?
You know. I saw there's a lot of space
outside your apartment.
Room enough for two beds.
- Yeah.
- We could make ourselves at home.
- We could move in.
- Come back every day?
- [Paul] Every day.
- Or you could give us a name.
[Patrick sighs]
There's only one name that I can give you
without destroying my livelihood.
- As a painter?
- [Patrick] No.
As a man who's had his family destroyed
by this fucking bullshit.
You got a pen. Mr. Billingsley?
[lock clicks]
[representative] Travel the Silo.
Today's for unity. family and friends.
Happy Forgiveness Day.
[citizens chattering]
[representative] Travel the Silo.
Happy Forgiveness Day.
[George] You know. people leave traces.
History is just traces
of a whole lot of people
over a whole lot of time.
Everything from the... the shirt on my back
to the... the... the shoes on our feet.
You know. if we wanted. we could pinpoint
the exact place that it was stitched
- or the person who wore it last.
- Really?
- The exact same?
- Yeah. uh-huh. Yes. the exact same.
- You want tea? Yeah.
- Uh. yeah. please.
Sorry. Continue.
- It's fascinating. though. right?
- Yeah. I mean. it's so fascinating.
- You don't appreciate that?
- [chuckling] No. I do.
[George exhales deeply]
Don't you ever think about the world
beyond the Silo?
No. When would I have time to do that?
Even now. I'm worried some idiot
is tightening the wrong bolts
or misreading the pressure valve.
You're looking at my beautiful face
and thinking about some idiot
with his pressure bolts.
- Pressure valve.
And yeah.
'cause your face kind of looks like one.
[chuckles] Sounds like the kind of thing
women and men in Mechanical dream about.
- Pressure valve.
- Oh. yeah?
Oh. definitely.
You know. while you're down here
dreaming of your world beyond worlds...
- You're the one that showed me this place.
- Yeah.
But I'm the one in Mechanical.
keeping you dreamers alive.
[George chuckles] Is that so?
Yeah.
'Cause I'm the one
that keeps things running.
[ticking]
- This must have taken you hours.
- [straining] Yeah. Time I don't have.
So...
why?
[breathes deeply]
'Cause when you talk about these things.
something ignites in you.
and I can see it on your face.
And I don't see that on a lot of people.
And. you know. w-whatever that feeling is.
when you feel it. I feel that too.
And it's not just here.
It's... It's afterwards.
[inhales deeply] It's... [exhales shakily]
What I'm trying to say is.
I fixed your watch for selfish reasons
'cause I really like the way that I feel
when I make you feel the way that you do.
[chuckles]
Hey. how'd you get it working?
It was easy to fix once
I'd made the right tools.
- You made the tools?
- Yeah.
Juliette Nichols.
you are truly... [kisses]
Okay. but shh.
- ...incredible.
- [Juliette chuckles]
[citizens chattering in distance]
[Juliette sighs]
- [cat owner] I know.
- [cat purrs. meows]
Soon. baby. Hmm.
- [knocking]
- [cat meows]
Regina Jackson?
Come in.
[door closes]
[Regina] Never thought I'd see that again.
I'm sorry. what?
That watch.
Huh. You know it?
Of course I do.
It belonged to my boyfriend.
So. how is George?
He's dead.
He fell off the stairs a few months ago.
[Regina] Mm-hmm.
- [smacks lips]
- [cat meowing]
Either of you know George.
or is the watch just something you found?
No. I worked with him
before I became sheriff.
- In Mechanical?
- Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Ms. Jackson. are you in possession
of any relics? Legal...
Last time I saw him.
that's where he was headed.
Moving on to the next thing.
The next person.
No. I don't have any relics. Not anymore.
Anything I had. and there was a lot.
I got for him.
Somebody give you my name?
Mm-hmm.
Happens a lot.
But I'm no dealer.
George had me buying things for him.
I come from a big family.
Lots of aunts. uncles. cousins.
He figured it would justify
the purchases if Judicial looked into it.
He had no one. so he used me to get them.
- All legal items? Or were there...
- Was your relationship sanctioned?
George didn't do sanctioned relationships.
And any fool would see he's not the type
of guy you spend forever with.
Legal? Sure. I guess.
But how does anyone know?
[Paul] You ask.
[Regina]
I walk into a law enforcement agency
and ask if the item I now possess
is an illegal possession?
Seems like I'm making it easy for them.
Did you see or hear from him
after he went down to Mechanical?
You ask a lot of questions.
Look. Sheriff.
George went down to Mechanical to explore
what he called "the big questions."
Illegal questions.
He got what he wanted from me.
He didn't need me anymore. so he left.
Probably in pursuit of someone new
down deep who could give him a hand.
What illegal questions
are we talking about?
I've been over this time and again
with Judicial.
Those aunts and uncles I told you about.
so have they.
George and those relics cost me a lot.
He lost his family.
but he didn't mind isolating me from mine.
He was good with words.
[Paul] Uh. thank you. uh.
f-for your time. Ms. Jackson.
- If you have any questions. we can def...
- [Regina] I do.
When he told you he loved you.
did you believe him?
Thank you.
[door closes]
[citizens chattering]
[Paul] There's no way
that woman's all there. right?
Her place is like
the junk room at Recycling.
And the smell of that cat food.
You all right?
Yeah. I'm great.
[knocking]
[Sims] We need the room.
Come on. man.
[Bernard exhales deeply]
[door closes]
There's an interview
with a confidential informant
that indicates the relic
you brought in earlier
was an illegal possession
belonging to your colleague.
George Wilkins.
I don't understand.
According to Judicial records.
a search was conducted
of Wilkins's place before he died.
In that search. they found nothing.
[Sims] But last night.
Wilkins's relic mysteriously appeared
in Trumbull's apartment
as a result
of a search coordinated by you.
First time I ever saw that relic
was last night in Trumbull's place
- when Billings showed it to me.
- Wait... [stammers]
Sims. George and I were friends.
Beyond this watch...
Oh. beyond that?
I never received anything from him.
especially something as ridiculous
as that thing.
[Bernard] I have a question.
For Mr. Sims.
On the day Judicial searched
George Wilkins's apartment.
was Trumbull a member of the search team?
Mayor. the name of Judicial's search team
members are strictly confidential.
You know that.
I am in no way required
to reveal that information
to the Sheriff's Department
or the Mayor's Office.
But if Trumbull was on that search team.
is it even slightly possible
that he simply thought
that the artifact was a harmless curio
and decided to take it home for himself?
You want me to entertain a hypothetical.
- I'm not going to do that.
- Theoretically. it is possible. Yes?
In your search.
did you find anything to explain
why Trumbull would wanna
murder Marnes and Jahns?
- No. Not yet. I...
- No. As far as everybody knows.
Marnes and Jahns died of heart issues
brought on by walking the Silo.
Any further investigation
might expose the truth.
and that could prove destabilizing.
[inhales deeply]
I know not everyone believes this.
but I've found that some mysteries
are best left...
[inhales deeply] ...unsolved.
Mr. Sims.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Thank you for not telling them
about me and George.
Did you plant that relic so I'd find it?
Your decision could've gotten me jailed
or even sent to clean.
[Juliette]
I wouldn't have let that happen.
You brought up my name with them
just as soon as they came at you.
Juliette. I have a family. A wife. a baby.
I know having some Judicial-minded deputy
who lives by every letter of the Pact
can be annoying.
But you have to be honest with me.
Honest. as if not only your life
but mine depended on it.
I'll try.
- [Paul] You'll try?
- Yeah. That's what I can do.
Juliette. you're the sheriff of the Silo.
and you can't commit
to being honest with me?
Shoot. maybe you and this George guy
were perfect for each other.
- You want honesty?
- I do.
Your hands shake.
You have flashes of pain.
Sheriff...
Under pressure.
you clench your hand so tight.
I'm surprised your fingers don't fall off.
You have the Syndrome.
And you're hiding it. So. Deputy.
living by the letter of the Pact.
you know it's a crime what you're doing.
not reporting yourself.
- I do.
- And according to the Pact.
you're in no way qualified
to be in a position of authority.
to have access to a firearm.
to detain criminals.
to even be a deputy in this department.
There's a way to do this.
And what you're doing now is not it.
- You called me dishonest.
- I did not.
- No?
- No.
I only asked you to be honest.
and if you weren't gonna be.
to let me know
rather than set me up to take the fall.
Everybody in the office says the reason
Holston and Marnes were a great team
was because they looked out
for each other.
And look what that got them.
[Paul] Good night. Sheriff.
[door opens]
- Shit.
- [door slams]
- [citizen] Hey. Happy Forgiveness Day.
- Hey.
[citizen 2] Happy Forgiveness Day. Deputy.
[citizens chattering]
[breathing deeply]
How was your day?
I've had better.
No lights tonight?
You know. my mother used to tell me
when I was a child that. um.
you shouldn't give up on the day.
even at the end of it.
'cause... [inhales sharply]
Well. she said that a... a whole day
could be saved with just a smile.
Lukas. you've never had a girlfriend.
have you?
Oh. tons.
Not one.
[Lukas] So many.
Like. every other level.
there is another lady friend.
Oh. and there. See?
There see what?
Smile. Like my mom said.
This was not with you. This was at you.
[breathes sharply]
[Lukas] I'll still take it.
You don't have your slate
with you tonight.
Well. a cafeteria worker
on my level told me
that. uh. it was gonna be cloudy
this evening. so I...
You came up anyway?
Yeah. I came to see you.
- [Lukas chuckles]
- Wow. that's terrible.
- [Juliette] Oh. wow.
- [stammers] That is a good line.
I didn't think it could get worse.
but you found a way.
Okay. well. you're still smiling.
so whatever.
Okay. I'll... Take care.
See you tomorrow. Sheriff?
- [chuckles. grunts]
- [baby giggling]
[door lock clicks]
[Kathleen] Honey?
[gasps] Who's here? Who's here?
- [Kathleen chuckles]
- [baby giggles]
[Kathleen] Oh! Oh. my goodness.
Mm-hmm. [chuckling] Yeah. [kisses]
Yeah.
[Kathleen chuckles]
- [softly] Hi.
- Hey.
[Paul groans] Oh. look at you.
How was your day? Daddy loves you.
[Kathleen] You okay? Look at your hands.
- Yeah. I'm okay.
- [Kathleen] Sit down.
[Paul exhales sharply]
- [Kathleen] Honey. please sit.
- [breathing sharply] Okay.
[Kathleen] Yeah.
Take off your shirt.
Did you eat the ginger root I gave you?
[Paul] I couldn't.
I wasn't alone at all today.
[Kathleen sighs]
She had you with her all day?
[Paul] Mm-hmm.
Finally trust you?
I don't think she's the trusting type.
[sighs]
She'll come around.
She should be honored to have you.
[sighs]
Honey. has it happened yet?
[Kathleen] What's that?
Have you seen any signs in Claire?
You know it doesn't work that way.
Just because you have it
doesn't mean she will.
But I worry.
[Kathleen] I know.
But right now. let's just worry
about getting you fixed up
so that you can get some sleep.
[Paul sighs]
Kath.
- Honey. you don't need to...
- I'm thankful for you and Claire.
I can't imagine life in the Silo
if I was all by myself.
[Paul breathes heavily]
[kisses]
[Juliette breathing deeply]
[exhales deeply]
- George?
- Mmm?
What's the big question?
Hmm. There's a lot of them.
What's outside?
What's beyond what the sensor can see?
Why are we here?
How long have we been here?
How much time do we have left?
But what's the biggest one?
[George breathes deeply]
What if everything you know to be true.
everything you've been told
by the people you love...
[clicks tongue]
...was in fact just one big lie?
[Juliette exhales deeply]
[machinery whirring]
[radio static]
Walk?
[radio clicks]
[Juliette] Walk?
- [radio clicks]
- Hey. it's late.
[radio clicks]
Yeah. it's so quiet.
It's time to come home.
[radio static. clicking]
Yeah?
[radio clicks]
Yeah. [sniffs] In the morning.
I'm gonna do what you said.
I'm gonna turn in the badge and resign.
[radio clicks]
S-So did you figure out what happened?
- [radio static. clicking]
- [chuckles]
No. couldn't give a fuck.
Turns out the person I was doing it for
wasn't worth the trip.
- so...
- [radio clicks]
[stammers] So did you leave here
and go all the way up top for him
or 'cause it was the right thing to do?
I mean. shit. the man's dead.
He didn't ask you to go up there.
- [radio clicks]
- It's just... It's a waste of time.
[scoffs] Time?
You got no concept of time.
You think you do. but you don't.
It's 'cause you got a whole lot more
ahead of you than behind.
Time to you is just an idea.
To me. it's years spent trapped
behind a closed door with memories.
All your friends and loved ones
somewhere out there.
the other side of it.
You can talk to me about time
when you can't
bring yourself to step out the door.
When seconds have become years.
[radio clicks]
He's not the person I thought he was.
[radio static. clicking]
What kind of a person are you?
The man you loved was murdered.
and now you're saying it's a waste of time
to find out why?
See. I don't know what happened.
but when you left here.
love had you trying to do the right thing.
And now anger is making you give up?
Fear did the same thing to me.
And that is a waste of time.
You're welcome to come here and join me.
Or you can stay where you are.
let go of whatever it is you're
wrestling with and finish the job.
It's your call.
[radio clicks]
[transmitter turns off]
[switch clicks]
You're going to be honest with me
this time.
What was I before?
You're the confidential informant.
the rat who gave up George.
You're the one
who told Judicial about the hard drive.
It's 'cause of you George is dead. Regina!
- Just give me a second.
- Give you a second?
You come to my door.
- and you accuse me of betrayal.
- You told Judicial about George.
- No. not them.
- No?
Judicial come during the day.
They ask the easy questions.
But the man who knows everything.
he comes at night.
- What? What are you ta...
- [shushes]
[fan clanking. whirring]
One night. I wake up.
and there's a man in my bedroom.
I can't see anything.
The lamp's been unplugged.
And he tells me t-to not move.
He wants me to tell him everything.
- To give up everybody. not just George.
- Regina. what do you...
For every one question I wouldn't answer.
he'd threaten two people I loved.
Two people I loved. My friends. my family.
If I left the apartment.
he'd turn up at night
at the foot of my bed in the darkness.
and he would recite the names of everyone
that I had talked to that day.
Everyone I had talked to.
If I had visitors...
Look. I put these up to block the sound.
I don't know if it works.
- Even with them. he may hear every word.
- Who is "he"?
Regina. who are you talking about?
They know how to get to you.
They know what you fear.
My mother...
every name I gave that man was another day
she didn't have to spend in the mines.
So yeah. I gave up
the names of every relic dealer I knew.
That's why Kennedy gave me your name.
Because he knew Judicial already had it.
Well. hopefully they all know
so they'll stay away from here.
- But if you cared for George...
- He only cared about himself.
Hey. George is dead
'cause you gave up his name.
He is dead
'cause he didn't give up the hard drive.
Oh. the fucking hard drive.
- Regina. what's on the hard drive?
- Don't ask.
What's on the drive?
I never saw.
[Juliette breathes heavily]
He never really cared about me.
He used me to get it for him.
Probably did the same to you.
pretending to love you
to get what he wanted.
I didn't give it to him.
Then he gave me something from his mother.
The only thing he kept of hers.
What did he give you?
These things. these objects. all this...
stuff.
Because of it. I have nothing.
I have no one.
I. um...
I'm sure the hard drive's been destroyed.
so I don't think
they're gonna disturb you anymore.
Neither will I. so...
Hey. um...
what did George give up
for the hard drive?
You said he gave you something.
What is it?
It's everything.
I don't think they know it exists.
They search and toss my place.
They look under the mat.
but they just toss the damn thing aside.
What is that?
This is a gift from George's mother.
given to him by his aunt. Gloria.
This was passed down
and hidden for generations.
[softly] Is this before the rebellion?
Was before the Silo.
Before there was a reason to lie.
When you see what you'll see.
don't speak it out loud.
Don't let them hear.
This will get you killed.
You have to wake him up.
But it's the middle of the night.
I know. but he has to see this.
Now.